# DEVDEEP BANERJEE

**Unreal Developer** 

+91 9916267332

6

devdeep01@gmail.com



/devdeep-banerjee



github.com/devdeep14



# PROFILE

Passionate game maker, completed Master's degree in Game Technology from ICAT Design & Media college. Having 4+ years of corporate experience as a digital designer in website design and development. Seeking an opportunity to enter the gaming industry having proficient knowledge in Game Development tools such as Unity and Unreal game engines with understanding of materials/shaders. Also, worked in 3D modeling tools like Maya and ProBuilder.

## GAME ENGINE SKILLS

devdeep14.github.io/devportfolio

- UNREAL ENGINE Good understanding of Unreal GUI, asset bundles, landscape, foliage,
- MATERIALS Knowledge of shader programming language (HLSL and GLSL)
- 3D MATH Strong base in linear algebra and vector math
- CODING Strong knowledge of C and C++ programming languages
- GRAPHICS LIBRARY Understanding of industrial standard graphics libraries OpenGL and DirectX

### EDUCATION

MASTERS IN
GAME TECHNOLOGY (MSc)

ICAT Design & Media College 2021 - 2023 Completing my masters in game technology from ICAT design & media college, affiliated to Alaqappa University

Learnt the basics of game design challenges & development process along with game engines such as Unity & Unreal with understanding of materials/shaders.

For final year project, working on an action-adventure FPS shooter game with sabotage missions on the backdrop of Kashmir, India.

BACHELORS IN COMPUTER APPLICATION (BCA)

Bangalore University 2013 - 2016 Completed my graduation in computer science from City College - Jayanagar, affiliated to Bangalore University

For final year project, created fully-functional insurance website which consists of purchase, claim & renew policy sections to manage user's account details

## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **DIGITAL DESIGNER**

Element14 Sept, 2019 - Sept, 2021 Part of Global Creative Services team, designing & developing complete marketing campaigns for element14 Asia-Pacific and clients based in Farnell EU & Newark NA

Creating form integrated landing pages & designing homepage leaderboard, supplier funded banners / product slots and merchandising eSpot banners

Brand reviewed marketing campaigns deployed across 42 sites in 26 languages, also worked in Adobe Target A/B testing for analyzing campaign results

#### **WEB DESIGNER**

CRMIT Solutions July, 2017 - July, 2019  Designing, developing & maintaining company website along with creating marketing emailer campaigns and product landing pages.

Creating visual imagery for company branding, creating corporate brochures, whitepapers, infographics and marketing slides

## COURSES

UNREAL ENGINE 5 C++ DEVELOPER

GameDev.tv Team - Udemy 2022 - 2023

• COMPLETE C# UNITY GAME DEVELOPER 2D & 3D

GameDev.tv Team - Udemy 2022 - 2023

## SKILLS

- C and C++
- Unreal Game Engine
- Maya and Zbrush
- Substance 3D
- HTML-CSS
- Bootstrap
- Photoshop / Illustrator
- Adobe XD / Figma

# KEY INTERESTS

- Game Concept & Ideation
- Game Design & Visualization
- Visual Motion Graphics

## SOFT SKILLS

- Critical-thinking
- Good communication
- Problem solving abilities

## HOBBIES











